Poland Subject Files, Inclusive: 1947-2002, undated, Bulk: 1960-1989
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Denominational Subject Files, 1954-2002, undated; 2
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 2-10 June 1979. Guide for Journalists, 1979 June 2-10 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 16-23 June 1983, 1983 June 1-15 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 16-23 June 1983, 1984 June 16-20 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 16-23 June 1983, 1985 June 21-25 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 16-23 June 1983, 1986 June 26-October (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland on 16-23 June 1983. Photo Clippings, 1983 June (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Third Visit to Poland on 8-14 June 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Third Visit to Poland on 8-14 June 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Visit to Poland, 2002 August (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Assassination Attempt, 1981 May-June (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Martial Law, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Individual Catholic Clergy. Pope John Paul II (Carol Wojtyla). Polish Renewal. Solidarity, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Clergy. Priesthood. Statistics, 1979-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. International Relations. Appeals. Solidarity. Contacts, 1980-1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Activities Disapproved by the State., 1966-1989, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Demonstrations. Protests, 1968-1988, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Defense of Believers' Rights. Litigation, 1979-1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement, 1974-1987, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement, 1981-1982, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Blachniki, Fr. Franciszek, 1982-1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Documents, 1980, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Congress "Nowy Chelowiek w Chrystusie." Papers, 1983 February 25-27 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Samizdat Publications, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Samizdat Publications, 1977-1980 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Samizdat Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Samizdat Publications, 1976-1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Oasis Movement. Samizdat Publications, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Christian Association of Workers, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Christian-Social Movement, 1980 May (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. National Association of Catholics, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for Self - Defense of Believers, 1978-1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Neokatekumenat (The Way), 1983, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Week of Christian Culture, 1978-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. The Festival of Sacrosong, 1974-1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Underground Publishing, 1980-1983, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Underground Publishing. Spotkania, 1978-1983, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Underground Publishing. Spotkania. Articles, 1978-1979, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Underground Publishing. Bukowinski, Fr. Wladyslaw, "Memoirs from Kazakhstan", 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Theology. Philosophy. Education. Morality, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Theology, 1970-1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Secular Education, 1973-1988, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Secular Education. The Catholic University of Lublin, 1966-1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Secular Education. The Catholic University of Lublin, 1981-1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Secular Education. The Catholic University of Lublin. Brochures, 1968-1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Secular Education. The Seminary of Catholic Theology, 1971-1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Theological Education, 1961-1998, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Religious Education and Children, 1966-1986, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Religion and Intellectuals, 1981-1988 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Statistics, 1966-1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Fellow Believers, 1973-1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Vatican, 1964-1973 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Vatican, 1974-1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Vatican, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Relations with Vatican, 1980-1999, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Polish Roman Catholic Communities Abroad, 1971-1982 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Polish Roman Catholic Missionaries Abroad, 1970-1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Broadcasts, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1985-2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Religion and National Identity, 1967-1985, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Involvement in Secular Affairs, Politics, 1978-1996 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs, 1967-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs, 1978-1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs, 1987-1993, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements, 1967-1987, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. PAX, 1956-1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. PAX, 1980-1986, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Christian Social Association (ChSS), 1980-1989, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. The Center for Documentation and Social Studies (ODISS), 1977-1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Polish Catholic-Social Union (PZKS), 1981-1988, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Polish Catholic-Social Union (PZKS), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Znak, 1965-1981, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Clubs of Catholic Intellectuals (KIK), 1976-1984, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Clubs of Catholic Intellectuals (KIK), 1981 July-October (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. University Chaplaincies, 1976-1983, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Pro-Patria, 1981, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Polish Academic Union (PZA), 1981 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Pro-Government and Catholic Movements. Caritas, 1975-1992 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church and Agricultural Funds, 1984-1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Arts. Architecture. Literature. Music, 1985-1998, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Women, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Children and Youth, 1965-1983 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Children and Youth, 1984-1989, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Sociology. Family, 1970-2001 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Visual Material, 1971-1988 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - United Evangelical Church, 1969-1990, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Uniate Church, 1968-1995, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)